Joshua Marcus Platform Engineer

Experienced and versatile Engineer with a background in Support, System Administration and IT as well as development teams. Comfortable and effective in almost any environment. Experience in healthcare and operating in a highly regulated environment. Work as both an individual contributor and manager, solid team player.

El Paso, TX 79930 +1 347 205-0416 joshmarcus85@gmail.com github.com/JMarquee85

SELECTED EXPERIENCE

Talkiatry, Remote

Platform Engineer/ Software Engineer

July 2021 - Present

- Write and debug applications and services in Typescript, Python, Bash, and other languages
- Configure and monitor CI/CD pipelines using CircleCI and GitHub Actions
- Design and configure Terraform modules to manage resources through IaC
- Administer a wide range of AWS services (ECS, EKS, Batch, S3, Lambda, Secrets Manager, etc.)
- Write applications and tools to solve issues
- Designed onboarding scripts and process for employee onboarding
- Managed Azure infrastructure and Enterprise Microsoft systems
- Previously served as Manager of IT Services over a team of six Systems Administrators

NYC Dept. of Health/ MTX, New York, NY

Advanced Technical Support Supervisor

February 2021 - July 2021

- Provided help desk support to medical and non-medical personnel distributing the COVID-19 vaccine
- Provided hardware and software support on iOS and Windows devices
- Interfaced with MTX management to ensure HIPAA compliance

InMotion Hosting, Virginia Beach, VA

Technical Support Representative

June 2017 - February 2018

- Provided Linux support or web hosting clients
- Provided technical support via phone, email, and live chat
- Diagnosed issues related to Wordpress and other content management systems
- Assisted customers with DNS setup for domains, mail, verification records, etc.

SKILLS

Python

Linux

Bash

AWS/ Azure

Terraform

CircleCI/ GitHub Actions

Git

Jira

Powershell

Typescript

Management

Microsoft

Windows

OSX

EDUCATION

William Paterson University

Master of Music

May 2022

Wayne, NJ

Eastern Illinois University

Bachelor's in Music

May 2010

Charleston, IL

OTHER

- CompTIA A+ Certified
- CompTIA Security+ Certified
- Azure Fundamentals